ttrate.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - TTRate.com Hong Kong - Local banks' latest and best foreign exchange rates

TTRate.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

What This Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how TTRate.com treats personal information that TTRate.com receives and collects, including information related to your use of TTRate.com's products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that TTRate.com does not own or control, or to people that TTRate.com does not employ or manage.

Information Collection and Use

TTRate.com collects personal information when you register with TTRate.com, when you use TTRate.com's products or services, when you visit TTRate.com pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. TTRate.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, occupation, and industry. For some products and services we might also ask for your address, phone number, business registration number, and information about you. When you register with TTRate.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

TTRate.com may collect personal information that you entered on some pages where you can submit information of other people to provide your requested service.

TTRate.com automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, TTRate.com cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.

We do not collect any financial information such as credit card and banking information.

We use the collected information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

We do not sell, share, rent, and otherwise intentionally made available your personal information to non-associated parties except to provide products or services that you have requested, we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  
We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with TTRate.com under confidentiality agreements.  
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of TTRate.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.  
After receipt of request based on the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance Section 58.  
We transfer information about you if TTRate.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, TTRate.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Cookies

TTRate.com may set and access TTRate.com cookies on your computer.

TTRate.com lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to TTRate.com's cookies.

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

You can edit your TTRate.com account information at any time.

Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

TTRate.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our site.

Please contact us if you have questions or suggestions.
